postpresso.com 2015-03-25

# Privacy Policy — Postpresso

## What this Policy Covers

Postpresso.com, (collectively "Postpresso") is committed to safeguarding your privacy online.  This Privacy Policy covers how Postpresso collects and manages the information, including personally identifiable information (collectively "Personal Information"), that is colles and receives through our website at www.postpresso.com (the "Site").  This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the Terms of Use Policy for our Site.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Postpresso does not own or control, to people that it does not employ or manage, or to any web site not owned by Postpresso to with our Site is linked.  If you have registered or otherwise provided your Personal Information to a third party web site which you have accessed via a link from our Site, that party will also have your Person Information.  Such third party websites have their own privacy statements, which are available for review directly on those various web sites.

## Your Consent to this Privacy Policy

By using our Site, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy, you may not use our Site. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please email us at support@Postpresso.com.

## Information Collection and Use

Postpresso collects Personal Information when you register with Postpresso or otherwise use our Site, or link to Postpresso partner sites or partner content. This Personal Information includes personally identifiable information as well as anonymous information. Once you register with and sign on to www.Postpresso.com, you are not anonymous to us. You are not required to provide personally identifiable information in order to use our Site. However, if you register on our Site, you will be required to provide certain personally identifiable information, which may include: your name or alias, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, credit card information (if you are making a purchase on our Site), mobile telephone number, and personal interests. The information that Postpresso possesses about you or collects concerning your transactions with us may be combined with information obtained from business partners or other companies. Postpresso automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page, product or service you request. Postpresso uses information to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our Site and services, contact you, conduct research, provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients, and for various other business purposes of Postpresso. Postpresso creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Postpresso does not rent, sell, or share personally identifiable information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except under the following circumstances:

• We may provide the information to trusted third parties who work on behalf of or with Postpresso. These companies may use your personally identifiable information to provide the information, products, or services you have requested from us, to help us communicate with you about offers, target ads, process your credit card transactions, assist with customer service, analyze data, and other services related to the business of Postpresso.

• We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

• We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Postpresso terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

• We may transfer your Personal Information as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation of Postpresso. If such a transfer occurs, the acquiring company’s use of your Personal Information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy, and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.

• We may inform advertisers of the results of our analyses of our server logs, including details regarding Site usage and general information about our audience, however, such disclosures will refer only to general, aggregate usage data from these analyses - never specific identifying information. • We may share your Personal Information with our affiliates, subsidiaries, or parent company.

• We may share your Personal Information from time to time with carefully selected third parties for marketing or other purposes not expressly described herein.

## Cookies and "Web Beacons"

Postpresso may set and access its cookies on your computer. Postpresso may also permit other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their own cookies on your computer. Postpresso may use “web beacons” in connection with our Site, products and services. These web beacons are not visible to the user. However, when a web beacon is opened or viewed, it causes certain information to be conveyed such as the time the email was read, the IP address, cookie information, a description of the page on which the web beacon resides, etc.

## Your Ability to Edit, Correct and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

You can access your account at anytime at www.Postpresso.com. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to our Site, products, or services, such as service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters. New categories of marketing communications may be added to Postpresso from time to time. You can delete your account by visiting the account management section at www.Postpresso.com. Some information may remain in our archived records during a reasonable period after your decision to terminate your account.

## Confidentiality and Security

Postpresso uses standard industry practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. Postpresso treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside of Postpresso. Unfortunately, perfect security does not exist on the Internet, and therefore, Postpresso makes no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures. Postpresso shall not be responsible for any damages that result from a lapse in compliance with this Privacy Policy because of a security breach, technical malfunction or similar problems.

## International Site Users

If you are located outside of the United States, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personally identifiable information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, you consent to the storage of such personally identifiable information on servers located outside your resident jurisdiction. By providing us with your personally identifiable information, you acknowledge that your have read this Privacy Policy, understand it, agree to its terms and consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information outside your resident jurisdiction.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Postpresso may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by placing a notice on our web site. This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 14, 2011.

## What is Our Policy Towards Users Under 21?

Postpresso products and services are not directed at users under 21. During the registration process on our Site we request that users provide their year of birth. Users under 21 are not permitted to sign up for a Postpresso account or to access or purchase its products or services. Customer Concerns If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please send us your feedback at support (at) salesbump.com
